A Guide to the Louis O. Kunkel papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA172
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence, 1930-1959; 3
  - Mi-Mu
    - Miller, G.L., 1940-1952; 25 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
      [Original file folder information "Stanley has correspondence. - (appears to be before 1945)]. At RIMR 1940-1945.
    - Miller, L.A., 4 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Millikan, D.F., 1947-1955; 22 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Milne, L.J., 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Miner, F.B., 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Mirsky, A.E., 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Missouri Agricultural Experiment Station, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Mitchell, W.H., 7 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Mittelstaedt, C.B.J., 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Mix, A.J., 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Monson, S.N., 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Montgomery County Sentinel, 4 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Moore, B., 1944 April 24-25 1945 April 23 1946 October 21-23; 7 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Meetings: Atending NAS meetings
    - Moore, J.D., 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Moore, J.I., 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Moore, S., 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Deals with honoring Dr. Gasser at dinner and presentation of volume containing reprints from each RIMR Member as gift. Kunkel contribution "Studies on a new corn virus disease"
    - Morel, G., 4 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Morgan, I.M., 1943 January 29; 6 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Meeting: RIMR staff meeting. Paper delivered "Virus transmissions thru dodder unions"
    - Morrell, J.E., 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Morris Foundation, 5 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Morton, H.E., 1 item (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Moseley, F.S., 5 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Mote, J.H., 1937 May; 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Meeting: Athens, Ga. University of Ga meeting of biologists. Paper delivered (Title unknown?)
    - Mott, P.B., 6 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Mount Holyoke College, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Mudd, S., 2 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Muesebeck, C.F.W., 7 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Mundkur, B.B., 6 items (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1932-1959; 2 folders
      Biographical material included in nominations for Holmes and Stanley.
      Includes some items submitted to the Proceedings.
      - 1932-1935 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - 1936-1959 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - National Research Council, 1930-1951; 108 items (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Dr. Kunkel retires as member of Board of National Research Fellowships in the Biological Sciences. Also served as member-at-large of the Division of Biology and Agriculture. Consists primarily of Correspondence with various members of board dealing with granting fellowships.
      Includes fellowship recommendations for: T.E. Rawlins, C.G. Vinson, A. Hollaender, L.K. Jones, I.D. Dobroscky and L.M. Black.
    - New York Botanical Garden, 1951-1960; 63 items (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Actively involved as member of various functioning administrative bodies of the N.Y. Botanical Garden and attends graduations and other functions involving N.Y. Botanical Garden.
      Includes: Member of Board of Managers, 1952-1961; Elected member of corporation in 1951 to elect Managers; Member of scientific committee 1953-1957; Recommendation of J.M. Fogg to Board of Managers; Includes also: typescripts of Dept reports and Foundations for 1956-57 appeals; Laboratory Research brochure; NY Botanical Garden reception for graduates. Kunkel awards certificates and gives small talk, June 20, 1957; 1960 a preliminary draft of a memorandum by Wm. C. Steere, Director "Planning for the New York Botanical Garden through the years" marked "Tentative and Confidential"; and pamphlet "Program of exploration in South America 1960-1969".
  - N-Nu (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Nagel, C.M., 1939 1947; 4 items
    - Nakata, K., 2 items
    - Narasimhan, M.J., 1 item
    - Nason, A., 3 items
    - NAC News, 1 item
    - Nash Automobile Co., 1 item
    - National Business Digest, 2 items
    - National City Bank of NY, 2 items
    - National Cyclopedia of American Biography, 11 items
    - National Science Foundation., 2 items
      Recommendation for A. Braun and K. Maramorosch for travel grants
    - Naval Personnel Bureau of., 1 item
      Recommendation for D. Faccini
    - Naylor, A.W., 3 items
    - Nebel, B.R., 4 items
    - Nebel, M.R., 2 items
    - Nelson, R., 1937 1957; 9 items
    - New England Wooden Ware Corp., 3 items
    - New South Wales Department of Agriculture, 2 items
    - New York Academy of Sciences, 3 items
    - New York Central Railroad, 1 item
    - New York Florists' Club, 1 item
    - New York Testing Laboratories, 2 items
    - Newton, N., 4 items
    - Niagara Sprayer Co., 2 items
    - Nichols, C.W., 2 items
    - Nichols, S.M., 2 items
    - Nicodemus, T., 2 items
    - Niederhauser, J.S., 11 items
    - Nolla, J.A.B., 6 items
    - North, D.S., 2 items
    - North Carolina Agricultural Experiment Station, 1 item
    - Northrop, John H., 1 item
      Northrop holograph
    - Norval, I.P., 1936-1939; 21 items
      Commonwealth Fund Fellow at RIMR 1936-1938. Includes evaluation and recommendations for.
    - Nugent, T.J., 2 items
    - Nutile, G.E., 2 items
  - O (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Ocfemia, G.O., 4 items
    - Ogata, T., 1 item
    - Ogilvie, L., 2 items
    - Olitsky, P.K., 1932 April; 1 item
      Meeting: RIMR staff meeting. Paper delivered (Title unknown?)
    - Olive, E.W., 2 items
    - Olmes, R., 2 items
    - Oltmanns, 1 item
    - Oman, P.W., 6 items
    - Opie, E.L., 2 items
      About dinner at Century Club before Dr. Stanley's Harvey Lecture
    - Oregon Agricultural Experiment Station, 1 item
    - Orpet, E.O., 3 items
    - Orsenigo, M., 3 items
    - Orton, C.R., 1931-1934, 1947; 15 items
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues. Includes recommendation for B. Sleeth for NRC fellowship.
    - Osborn, H. Jr. At RIMR, 1932-1939; 10 items
      Includes Correspondence to S. Flexner recommending Osborn for RIMR position.
    - Oster, Gerald. At RIMR, 1945-1948; 8 items
    - Osterhaut, W.J.V., 4 items
      Member RIMR. Includes letters of congratulations on Kunkel becoming Member RIMR and NAS.
    - Ousley, G. 1932 Sept. begins work as greenhouse foreman of RIMR Princeton, 6 items
      1932 Sept. begins work as greenhouse foreman of RIMR Princeton.
    - Overpeck, J. C, 92 items
  - P-Pe (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Pachlett, I., 2 items
    - Pal, B.P., 1 item
    - Pal, O., 1 item
    - Palade, G., 1 item
      Holograph
    - Palm, B.T., 1932 1950; 5 items
      Includes evaluation of Palm's work.
    - Palmer, R.G., 7 items
    - Palmiter, D.H., 8 items
    - Pan American Medical Assocation, 2 items
    - Pan-Pacific Union, 1 item
    - Pantages, S., 2 items
    - Parducci, R., 2 items
    - Parfentjev, I.A., 2 items
    - Paris, H.M., 4 items
    - Parker, K.G., 1936 1951; 8 items
    - Parker, R., 2 items
    - Parris, G.K., 5 items
    - Patch, R.H., 4 items
    - Patel, M.K., 1 item
    - Patmore, M.V., 1 item
    - Pauling, L., 1 item
    - Pawlychenko, T.K., 2 items
    - Payne, G.C., 5 items
    - Payne, J., 1 item
    - Peace, T.R., 2 items
    - Pearson, P.B., 2 items
    - Peirce, G.J., 2 items
    - Peltier, G.L., 1931 1951; 5 items
    - Pennsylvania Agricultural Experiment Station, 1 item
    - Penzkofer, F., 2 items
    - Pepper, B.P., 2 items
    - Perkins, D.D., 1 item
    - Perry, B.A., 2 items
    - Perry, J.T., 4 items
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital, 2 items
    - Peterson, K.D., 2 items
    - Peterson, P.D., 2 items
    - Pethybridge, G.H., 3 items
  - Pe-Py
    - Petrakis, M.M., 4 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Petre, A.W., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pfeiffer, C.L., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Philadelphia, City Trusts of, 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Phytopathology, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pierce, W.H., 4 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pinckard, J.A., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pincus, J.W., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pirone, P.P., 1934 1940; 7 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Plank, H.K., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Plantenga, H., 1932-1933; 10 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Volunteer RIMR
    - Plus, N., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pollard, M., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pon, D.S., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pontis, R.E., 3 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pope, F.J., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Popp, H.W., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Poos, F.W., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Porges, N., 6 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Porter, D.R., 3 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Porter, H.L., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Porter, J.R., 3 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Porter, K.R., 1945 May 11; 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Meeting: RIMR staff meeting. Paper delivered "Some characteristics of yellows viruses"
    - Posnette, A.F., 4 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pound, G.S., 7 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Prado, F.A. del, 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Press Photographers' Assoc of N Y, 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Princeton Bank and Trust Co., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Princeton Motor Shop, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Princeton University, 1945-1948; 5 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Includes Correspondence about reelection (1945-1948) as member on the Advisory Council, Dept of biology, Princeton Univ.
    - Princeton University Press, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Provident Mutual Life Insurance Co., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pruthi, H.S., 6 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Concerns examination of N.C. Chatterjee thesis and recommendation for degree granting
    - Purvis, E.R., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pyfrom, H.T., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Price, Wm. C., 1930-1954; 85 items (Box 12, Folder 6)
      At RIMR 1932-1945. Professional Correspondence between colleagues socially friendly. Includes Price 1930 reprint and typescript of summary of Price thesis; Price thank you letters for RIMR contributions to Phytopathology as Editor- in-chief.
  - Q (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Queensland Forest Service, 3 items
  - Raychaudhuri, S.P. At RIMR 1950-1952, 1947-1958; 81 items (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Correspondence includes various recommendations for; work evaluation while at RIMR of; curriculum vitae; 8 items of Raychaudhuri's Correspondence left at RIMR when returned to India.
  - R-Re (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Rake, G.W., 3 items
    - Ramos Nobrega, N., 2 items
    - Rand, F.V., 2 items
    - Rankin, W.H., 3 items
    - Rappaport, I., 1 item
    - Rappaport, J., 2 items
    - Rastetter, L. & Sons, 1 item
    - Rawitscher, F., 7 items
    - Rawlins, T.E., 1931 1950; 10 items
    - Rayner, M.C., 1 item
    - Realberg, L., 3 items
    - Reddick, D., 5 items
    - Redmann, R.G., 2 items
    - Redfield, A.C., 1 item
    - Redmond, W.B., 1 item
    - Reed, C.A., 1 item
    - Reed, G.M., 1931-1942; 33 items
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues socially friendly
    - Reed, H.S., 4 items
    - Reed, L.N., 14 items
    - Reed, M.D., 5 items
  - Re-Ri
    - Reeves, E.L., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Reeves, R.E., 5 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Reichert, J., 1937 1958; 4 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Reinhardt, G.N. Co., 4 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Reinhold, A.P., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Reinking, O.A., 10 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Includes recommendations for A.J. Ullstrup and C.E. Yarwood.
    - Reisner, J.H., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Remington Rand Inc., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Reppa, H., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Republican National Committee, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Rex, E.G., 1938 1951; 5 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
      1938; 1951 Meeting. Includes 1951 Nov 6 West Springfield, Mass. Northeastern division of American Phytopathological Society meeting. Paper delivered "A review of 40 years of research work in the field of plant viruses".
    - Reynolds, B.D., 6 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Correspondence about O.E. White retirement and Kunkel contribution and memorial letter
    - Reynolds, E.S., 8 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Rhoads, C.P., 1933 January 20; 5 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Meeting: RIMR staff meeting. Paper delivered "Similarities between the diseases of the vegetable kingdom and those of man and animals" and recommendation for Gerald Oster
    - Rhode Island Agricultural Experiment Station, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Riblett, E.W., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Rich, G.M., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Richey, F.D., 1909; 2 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
      On attending 40 anniversary of Class of 1909 at Columbia, Mo. State University of Mo.
    - Richmond, R.G., 4 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Rickett, H.W., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Ridgway, E.P., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Riker, A.J., 1932-1949; 66 items (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Includes Riker biographical material with bibliography.
  - Ri-Ry (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Riley, H.P., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Riley, V., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Roane, C.W., 6 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Roberts, E.A., 1932 1954; 10 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Roberts, E., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Roberts, J.W., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Roberts, R.H., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Robertson, N., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Robinson, F.S., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rochow, W.F., 13 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Correspondence with F.B. Hanson
    - Rodenhiser, H.A., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rodgers, A.D. III, 5 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Roger Smith Hotel, 1940 April 22; 1 item (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Meeting: Washington, DC NAS meeting
    - Rogers, C.H., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rogers, J., 4 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rohde, R., 4 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rhm and Haas Co., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rohrs, W., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Roque, A., 4 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
      About F.E. Holmes visits. and investigative work at Agricultural Experiment Station, Puerto Rico
    - Rose Mfg. Co., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rosen, H.R., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Ross, J., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
      About purchasing journals for library
    - Ross, W.A., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Routien, J.B., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rothbard, S., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rous, P., 1934-1956; 13 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Member RIMR. Professional Correspondence between colleagues
    - Royce, G.G., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rudorf, W., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
      George H. Shull biographical material
    - Rue, J.L., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rundlett, E., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Ruppel, R.F., 8 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Includes college transcript and bibliography.
    - Ryan, F.J., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Ryerson, K.A., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Evaluation of Dmitri Borodin's work
    - Robbins, Wm. J., 1933-1959; 55 items (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues. Includes Kunkel letter of congratulations to Robbins on appointment as Director N Y Botanical Gardens and Professor of Botany, Columbia Univ; also recommendations for C.E. Yarwood, G.L. McNew, R.F. Dawson, A.C. Braun.
    - Ross, F.A., 1937-1956; 40 items (Box 13, Folder 6)
      At RIMR 1937-1940. Includes: recommendation for; typescripts of Ross presentation "The effect of proteodastic enzymes upon purified preparations of the virus of mosaic disease of tobacco" and Ross unpublished work on plant viruses; Ross et al reprint "The problems of causes of blackening in cooked potatoes".
  - S-Sch
    - Sabin, A.B., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Sabin, Florence R. Member RIMR, 1935-1951; 6 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Includes Correspondence about contribution for Flexner medal; recommendations for P.A. Munz, G.N. Jones, A.S. Crafts for Guggenheim fellowships: Kunkel letter of congratulations on Dr. Sabin's 80 birthday.
    - Sadasivan, T.S., 4 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Sager, R., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Sakimura, K. At RIMR for 6 months beginning 1948 Apr, 12 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
      At RIMR for 6 months beginning 1948 Apr. Includes biographical material.
    - Salaman, R.N., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Saltonstall, R., 6 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Samson, J.W., 1950 December 20; 2 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Meeting: Concerning 1950 Dec 20 (Correspondence indicates given in the section on microbiology - Location?) Paper delivered "The relationship between plant and animal neoplasms"
    - Samson, R.W., 5 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Samuel, G., 4 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Includes congratulations to Dr. Kunkel on election to NAS and on becoming head of RIMR Plant Pathology laboratories.
    - Sanders, E.H., 4 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Sanford, G.B., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Sarles, M.P., 1932 March 21; 4 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Meeting: RIMR staff meeting. Paper delivered "Local lesions in the isolation and identification of plant viruses"
    - Sauer, C.A., 1 item (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Recommendation for Miss Zeliaette Troy
    - Savage, M., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Scaglirla, J.D., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Schaffer, N., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Schaffnit, E., 7 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Scherr, G.H., 3 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Schmidt, C.L.A., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Recommendation for T.E. Rawlins
    - Schoombec, N.F., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Schroeder, W.T., 2 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Schulman Printing Co., 4 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Schultz, E.S., 1932-1954; 40 items (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Sch-Se (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Schultz, E.W., 3 items
    - Schumacher, G., 5 items
    - Science, 3 items
    - Scientific Monthly; Science Press. Manuscript, 1933 December; 5 items
      Includes items about publishing Kunkel ms "Pests away from home" in 1933 Dec. Scientific Monthly.
    - Science Press Printing Co., 1934-1944; 34 items
      Matters concerning Kunkel and staff mss publications in Phytopathology and 1 ms in The Botanical Review
    - Science Service. Deals primarily with 1933 Mar 31 radio talk "Pests away from home" [Editor's note: Typescript of radio talk See under: Biographical material in Box no. 1], 1933 March 31; 14 items
      Typescript of radio talk See under: Biographical material in Box no. 1.
      Deals primarily with 1933 Mar 31 radio talk "Pests away from home". Includes press release reporting radio talk prepared for newspapers and magazines.
    - Scoggin, J.K.
      See under: Thurlow, J.F. Box no. 15
    - Scott, C.E., 1943 1953; 2 items
    - Scottish Horticultural Research Institute, 1 item
    - Scroggs, S., 2 items
      Recommendation for K. Starr Chester
    - Scully, P.H., 3 items
    - Seaver, F.J., 2 items
    - Sehgal, O.P., 4 items
    - Seiffert, G., 1 item
    - Sellew, M.B., 2 items
    - Settel, S., 4 items
  - Se-Si
    - Severin, H.H. 1931-1948., 1930-1948; 16 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues. Includes Severin bibliography (1930-1948).
    - Shapiro, S., 4 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shapovalov, M., 1935-1952; 17 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues socially friendly. Includes translation of program of 1935 Dec 14-17 U.S.S.R. Academy of Sciences, All union Conference for the study of ultramicrobes and filterable viruses; 1 item to Leo Shapalov (son); Kunkel attends 1952 Oct 9-11 Berkeley, California opening ceremonies of new biological and virus laboratory of Univ. of California at Berkeley.
    - Sharp, L.W., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Sharp, S.S. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shaw, J.K., 3 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shaw, L., 8 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shaw, W.B., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shear, C.L., 3 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shearer, W.S., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shelhorse, B.L., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shelton, E.M., 3 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shepley, H.R., 4 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
      About treatment for diseased Euonymus vines in the court of Harvard Medical School
    - Sherbakoff, C.D., 1932 1949; 4 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Sherwood, S.F., 1937 1946; 4 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shifriss, O., 3 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shipman, E.F., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Curriculum vitae
    - Shoreham Hotel, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shull, C.A. [Editor, Plant Physiology], 25 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
      About setting policy for RIMR aid to Plant Physiology for publication of mss.
    - Shull, G.H., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Kunkel's attitudes toward playground development at Princeton on land formerly used as experimental field
    - Shull, J.C., 4 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Shuttleworth, F.S., 4 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Siegel, A., 3 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Includes curriculum vitae with bibliography.
    - Siegler, E.A., 4 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Sigma Xi, 1932-1942; 98 items (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Correspondence about: 1933 Apr 18 Princeton, N.J. RIMR Dept of Animal and Plant Pathology Kunkel demonstration on "Isolation of pure cultures from mixtures of the viruses of tobacco and aucuba mosaics" with program of meeting; evaluations of W.C. Price and W.M. Stanley work with recommendation for Sigma Xi awards for Price and Stanley; Lectures: Arrangements for 1937 June Sigma Xi lecture series "Frontiers in Science". Paper delivered "New views in virus disease research". Presented at Palo Alto, Calif. Stanford Univ. (June 1), Palo Alto, Calif. Stanford Univ. (June 4), Columbia, Mo. Univ. of Mo. (June 8). Published in 1939 in "Science in Progress" by Yale Univ. Press.
      Also includes some duplicated material announcing meetings, nominations, lectures, speakers, topics.
      1942 Nov 17 typescript of minute in memory of Wade Brown by Louise Pearce, R.W. Glaser and L.O. Kunkel. Prepared for Sigma Xi.
  - Si-Sm (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Silberschmidt, K.M., 1944-1954; 28 items
      Includes recommendation for G.T.A. Benda.
    - Simons, J., 2 items
    - Sinclair, J.R., 2 items
    - Sinnott, E.W., 1931-1953; 15 items
    - Sistrom, W., 4 items
    - Skalweit, M., 3 items
    - Skidelsky, S.H., 2 items
    - Slock, D.A., 4 items
    - Sloan, M.J., 4 items
    - Slobohm, D.C., 2 items
    - Smadel, J.E. Meeting, 1940; 9 items
      Includes 1940 May 24 RIMR staff meeting. Paper delivered "Filter-passing saprophytes in plant juices".
    - Small, S.J., 4 items
    - Smalle, D.E., 3 items
    - Smith, A.G. Jr., 1 item
    - Smith, F.F., 1936-1953; 29 items
    - Smith, G., 2 items
    - Smith, G.A., 1 item
    - Smith, G.H., 4 items
    - Smith, G.M., 1 item
    - Smith, Gertrude C., 2 items
    - Smith, H.W., 2 items
    - Smith, J.H., 6 items
  - Sm-St
    - Smith, K.M., 1932-1952; 36 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
      At RIMR 1939 Apr-June on RF Fellowship. Correspondence includes fellowship recommendation for; recommendation for awarding N.C. Chatterjee Doctor of Science degree from Univ. of Bombay.
    - Smith, L.C. Typewriters Inc., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Smith, L.T., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Member of honorary committee for NYC 300 anniversary celebration
    - Smith, M.A., 7 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Smith, P.H., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Smith, T.A., 4 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Smithburn, K.G., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Smithsonian Institute, 1946 October 23; 2 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
      1946 October 23. Dr. Kunkel attends reception to commemorate 100 years since founding of
    - Snyder, W.C., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 4)